Hello everyone, good evening. Can you hear my voice?
If you can, you can poke a 1.
I am today's host, Lydia, and I will show you how to make a 3D sunscreen suit.
OK, so today's content is mainly divided into three parts.
The first part is about a change.
We can see the effect of the change before and after the change.
The second part is to make some details on our clothes,
including our elastic band, pleats, double-headed zipper, sewing pleats, and the appearance of our sunscreen suit.
At the same time, the third part is also about the performance of the final effect.
I will show you an automatic 3D sticker,
and the green color of the 3D effect.
These two new functions are the main functions to be introduced in our 2024.1 version.
OK, let's start tonight's live broadcast.
First of all, we can see that this time we have a material to share with you about this sunscreen suit.
In the material, you can open our virtual model.
This virtual model is also from us.
The official material of our Kinect is a female model with no face.
It is convenient for us to show a model without the need for these accessories.
Then we open our clothing file.
At the same time, it is also an downloaded file on the official account.
After opening, we can see that our clothing and our model now have a transparent effect.
We can use our automatic wear function.
We can automatically wear our clothes to a current model.
The automatic wear function has a bottom logic.
It is because our virtual model has the information of our sunscreen suit.
You can see the virtual model information display here.
It shows a virtual model's sunscreen suit.
The black grid represents that our virtual model has a sunscreen suit.
Our Kinect official models all have this sunscreen suit information.
Once we have this sunscreen suit information,
our clothing is simulated by the virtual model with the information of the sunscreen suit.
Then we automatically wear it to other models.
It can automatically adapt to the appropriate position.
So it is a very convenient function.
Then you can also use it.
When we put on this clothes,
this is our basic clothing.
First, let's organize our 2D version.
First, we can go to the screen.
First, we can delete some unnecessary panels.
For example, this virtual panel is our storage panel.
We don't need it.
We can delete it.
Then, if we do this style today,
I don't need to make a division.
So we can delete our middle panel.
Then put the front panel in the position of our model shadow.
Then put the sleeves panel next to it.
Then put the back panel next to it.
Then we can see that this is our sleeves on this side.
Then this is the sleeves on the other side.
So we usually line up our 2D panel like this.
Then after the panels are all lined up,
we continue to make a change.
First of all,
we are in the position of the front panel.
Then I switched to our hook wheel.
I use the shortcut key I.
Then, we are in the inner line.
We are in the position of the inner line.
To make a cut.
The front panel is also cut here.
After the cut is done,
I fix the unnecessary panel.
We have to delete it.
Then we can see the unnecessary internal line.
When we select this line,
if two lines appear,
it means that there are multiple lines here.
The red line represents our internal line.
The black line represents our panel.
Then we don't need the internal line, we delete the internal line
Then here is also
Then we will merge our version
Then the back is the same
After merging, this is a sample of our base
Then let's make a change
I suggest that everyone can confirm the basic sample
After confirmation, we will make it a column reference line
This function is
It is convenient to compare the difference between a sample before and after we change the money
Only need to use our adjustment version tool
After selecting the version, right-click on the version
Then find the function of the column as a reference line in our pop-up menu
We are now on the column reference line
Of course you can't see it now
We have to do an edit on the version
You can see it
You can see its display
Now I will use the edit version tool to edit our version
For example, I will make a change to the bottom
When I change it, I can control our direction
You can see this is our reference line, right?
If this reference line
I don't like the length I changed now
I want to go back to the original length
Then I can use the looping tool to connect our reference line
Let's take a look
You need to make all three edges a choice
Then press the return key
Then hook it up
After hooking up
We switch to our edit version tool
Then select the bottom and inner line we just made
Then right-click
Then let's take a look
There is a change to the outside of the version
Then we can just
The version we just changed
Return to our original state
Then this reference line will also display here
So our reference line
You can use it like this
Then we
Take a look
We can do it in 2D
To shorten our version
We can also do it in 3D
Before we do it in 3D
Let's take a look
Because we just deleted the version
So our zipper is gone now
Add the zipper first
This is our zipper function
Then directly in 3D
Let's add it
I'll simulate it
After the zipper is added
We now select our tool
To our shape line tool
The shape line tool
Is our 3D version
A very useful tool
It is divided into edit shape line
Zipper shape line
Mobile shape line
And the configuration shape line
Now I want to use this tool
To shorten a version
What I used
Is our zipper shape line
That's all you need
On our costume
Log in
Activate this tool
Then you can see our
I'm sorry
This should be a mistake
Mobile shape line
Zipper is on the dimension
Zipper
That move
Is our one
Then you can see
That the dimension
You can move it
You can change the length
And the length
We can do it over here
A pull
Pull
At the same time
We can click
Our mouse right arrow
Is a distance you want to move
I can enter one
A defined value
Make a pull
After that
We'll simulate it
In this way
We can do this
The costume
In 3D
Make a direct change
A direct
Shorten
Its one-way change
OK, that's our one
Next, we will change the dimension of the clothing.
I want to introduce the function of joint editing in the dimension section.
Before we talk about joint editing, let's take a look at the sewing line in the middle.
And I want the side seam to be a whole seam, so that it is convenient for me to do joint editing.
So I first delete the sewing line on the side seam.
Then we sew the side seam all the way up.
Then I switch to the editing sewing line tool.
Select our sewing line and right-click to find our joint line.
The new function of the joint line is also considered a new function.
Although it is not in this version, it is a new function of the previous two versions.
Maybe you haven't used it too much yet, so you can take a look.
After we set up the function of the joint line, it has a small arrow symbol on the sewing line.
Then prove that the joint line is set up.
After we set it up, we will continue to edit it.
For example, I use this editing tool to select these three lines.
There is also a multi-line selection here.
Select the outside line of our board.
Then I pull it.
At the same time, I can control it.
For example, I will widen it by 50.
I widened it here.
See, due to the relationship of joint operation, my side is also widened by 50.
So our joint function is very convenient to edit our board.
This is a multi-line selection.
After we finish editing here, remember to simulate it in the 3D window.
OK, for the same operation, we also set up a multi-line for the joint line.
Then we lower the position of the joint line.
To control the direction of the joint line, we press the Ctrl key.
Then the joint line is lowered to the side.
This line is in a state that is almost parallel to it.
OK.
Then this is the joint.
Since we just pulled it here, the joint is not enough.
So in theory, if you widen it, the joint will be larger.
So we also move it down a little bit here.
Then press the Ctrl key.
Then we can also see that while we are pulling, there is a angle here.
You can see that the green line is now 97.4 degrees.
Then we give it about 90 degrees.
That is, if we fight these two sides, it should be around 180 degrees.
Anyway, it's 90 degrees up and down.
Then simulate it again.
In this way, the dimension of the joint and the shape of the joint are almost the same.
OK.
When we simulate here, we slightly drag the joint down a little bit.
Because we are moving it all the way here.
So its joint length is now relatively long.
It is relatively long.
OK.
Then now let's change this sleeve.
The two panels can be put up a little bit.
OK.
Let's change this sleeve first.
As for the sleeve, we first change this line to a straight line.
We directly delete this straight line point in the middle with the edit panel tool.
Then if you want to add a straight line point in the cutout position,
we can use the cutout tool.
The cutout tool.
Press the right button directly to increase the cutout position.
Then we change this line to the length of these two lines.
Right.
We can use the edit panel tool to take a look first.
Now this length is 412.
Right.
Then we use the change length.
Choose two lines.
Then find the change length.
Then enter the length we want.
412.
You can see that it is now increasing in one direction.
Then we need to increase it in two directions at the same time.
We need to determine the direction below as two sides,
which is our both.
Then click OK.
OK.
Then copy it at the same time.
Then we now pull this sleeve a little bit.
Because I want to do a big thumb and there is a design that moves.
So I pull the sleeve down as much as possible.
Then I go to find the position of this movement.
And when you pull it,
Don't twist it, if you twist it, the position may not be very good.
As much as possible, look at this side is a relatively smooth state, remember to turn off the simulation.
Then we can open our semi-transparent display in our 3D window.
There is a clothing rendering type on our side, open our semi-transparent display, the key is 2 plus 4.
Then we find the position of the wrist, point a small blue dot here.
Then on our 2D window side, we can see a small blue dot display at the same time.
Then we can find our internal multilayer line tool.
Then we will create an internal line near this small blue dot.
After creating an internal line, we can make a tight seam for it.
After the tight seam is done, we will switch the texture surface back to the thick texture.
OK.
Then we just cut off a single Shoukofu plate from the sleeve.
The Shoukofu plate must be a T-shape.
So we want to change the position of the bottom to a vertical state from this point up, right?
OK.
Now we can right-click on this point.
Then find our deep vertical internal line.
Then it should be X-axis.
OK.
Then just use the default option.
The default is a 90-degree vertical.
Of course, you can also manually input the specific angle value you want.
OK.
The same goes for this side.
After that, we select these two lines and cut them off.
After cutting them off, we switch to the adjustment plate tool.
Then delete it.
You can see that our Shoukofu line is still there.
Even if we cut off the plate, it will still have the original Shoukofu line.
If we don't need this Shoukofu line, we can right-click on it.
There is a delete Shoukofu line on the right.
Yes, it's here.
Delete Shoukofu line.
After deleting it, you can see that it's gone.
And if you want to delete this large plate,
for example, you don't want to see this Shoukofu line anymore,
and you want to hide it,
then we can also have a display Shoukofu line option here in our costume.
You delete it.
Our Shoukofu line is hidden.
We can hide it now.
And we just listed this internal line.
We don't need it.
Let's delete it.
OK.
Then after we finish here, we simulate it.
Oh, we have to adjust the seam line here.
Because we just cut it off here.
Cut it off.
So first of all, let's sew these two sides together.
After sewing it together,
it must have to adjust the seam line here.
We select the edge seam line.
Pull this seam line to the head, right?
Pull it to the head.
Let me show you.
That's right.
And our sleeve is actually a little tight at the bottom.
I want to let it go a little bit.
Can we widen it?
If you want to widen it, we still use this length adjustment tool.
Then widen it in two directions.
And now it's 265.9.
Then we'll just add it to 280.
Widen it a little bit.
You can even add it to 290.
This depends on your own design.
After widening, we are now going to do the design of the hole.
The design of the hole is also.
We have already worn the thumb here.
There is a position.
Then we also point a small blue point here.
And then here we go.
We are going to use the internal multilayer line.
Draw an internal line.
And then the internal line.
Make a tight seam.
After the tight seam is finished, we.
You can use the edge seam line tool to adjust it.
Adjust the seam line a little bit.
At this time, we can simulate it.
Let this thumb come out.
Come out.
And then on top.
We're going to sew it with free sewing.
Add the sewing line you need.
It's about this effect.
What about the sewing line below?
If you need to come up a little bit.
You can edit it again.
Right?
OK.
Then we have such an opening design.
Not finished yet.
There is one here that needs to be combined.
Two lines.
Combine it.
Because we're opening it here now.
So these two lines should be combined.
OK.
Combine.
After the combination.
We have this board.
Let me show you.
It's done.
After completion, we can take a look.
We are.
One side is OK.
What about the other side?
Maybe this place.
Is it not worn well?
At this time.
We can use our.
Select both of these boards.
Select the right button at the same time.
Direct use of our.
Application symmetry.
One of the functions.
Then.
It can be synchronized.
To simulate.
A corresponding board.
It's symmetrical.
This board.
Symmetrical.
The board.
OK.
What about this?
It's one of ours.
The sleeve.
A small design of the thumb movement.
That's it.
OK.
Now.
Let's take our.
Let's do this.
Loose belt.
It's one of our.
A position.
I want to make it.
A closure.
A closure of the loose belt.
That's it.
A closure of the loose band.
A closure of the loose belt.
The design.
Then I need to.
To.
Assembly.
An.
Your.
Get.
By the length of snow.
The length of the school box is five ninety.
Five
Ten.
Bat ....
Then.
I'm collecting tools.
Result tool.
Let's.
It is now in a state of equal length with our bottom line
But our loose tie
It must have a tightening effect, right?
Then we give it an 80% tightening effect
Then I'm going to weigh it
Then we have a built-in calculator function here
You can take a look
All the frames that need to be entered
You just have to select the data you want to enter
There is a calculator on the right
Then we can click here
Then you use the digital keyboard
You input 590 x 0.8
You can also get the data we want
Then we click to confirm
This is the length we want, right?
You can also use this small built-in calculator
Sometimes do some simple calculations
Then we will do a symmetrical link with this board
Right click on this board
Give it a symmetrical edit sewing line, right?
Okay, then we're going to sew it
Before sewing
We need to make this two-centimeter internal line for him
Put it on
Then use our line sewing tool
And then
Press our F key
A seam of 1 to N
And then below
Okay, after sewing this
Everyone pay attention
Then our sewing
Is it a board outside the line
With a board outside the line
And this board must be
A relationship that overlaps
So we need to change our sewing line type
Change to fold
The fold of the sewing line type
Before we need to use this
A selection of pull-down
To choose
Now, our UI has been updated
In the version of 2024.1
Became a hook and loop
More intuitive
And we also have a shortcut key
Is the one next to our wheelbarrow key
The symbol of the single and double shadows
We just need to press this one
You can see our fold
This place has been selected
So we will change this later
The sewing line type
Will be more convenient
Okay, after we change it
Switch to the adjustment board tool
Directly put this board
And then use its sewing line relationship
Add it to the inside
And then don't forget
We have a small section here
Remember to sew
That's the same
I also use this shortcut key
Change the sewing line type
And then simulate
Okay, that's it
Okay, after we do this
I will save this file
Because I haven't saved it from the beginning
Save it
Save it to the live material
Okay
After saving it
Let's move on to the sun visor
Now
We have finished the
Sleeveless
And now let's talk about this hat
For hats
Like our sun visor
Usually there will be one
More out of the hat
To carry out a better
A better coverage effect
Right
Okay, what about this hat
We can also go to
Create such a board
First of all, let's go to it
Make a positioning
Probably
I want to be in this position
To add such a
The board of the hat
In our
Wait a minute
We have to do this
Do this
The position of this plate
Okay, first of all
Let's add a point
Add a point
Use this position
Add a straight line point
And then
Use
Editing tool
Select our
One
Such a
Let me take a look
This board seems
Accidentally
Just now
Maybe at the beginning
I see
It seems to be at the beginning
I accidentally adjusted it
I adjust it again
I adjust it back
It has a reference line
Just right
I adjust it back
It should be like this
The width should be like this
Then
If this is the curve
Here
Adjust it
When we are not careful
An uncautious
A careless
It should be like this
The width should be like this
And then
This curve
Adjust it here
We are not careful
At first
It doesn't matter, we just need to adjust it a little bit.
OK.
Let's simulate it after we've done that.
It might start to...
Let me see, this point should be...
Sorry, increase the point to the 100% line.
This should be 25.
The inner line should be reduced.
OK.
Let's align the seam line.
There's a 8.3 missing here.
That means I need to add another 8.3 to this point.
This should be OK.
It's even. OK.
Let's continue.
The original pattern of this hat is a bit problematic.
I'll delete this curve point with our edit curve point tool.
It's a bit round here.
OK, we've just talked about our hat.
After adding a straight line here,
let's measure the width of the hat.
Select this edge and this edge.
Let's see, it's 293 now.
293.
Let's use our curve point tool.
Draw a 293 in the blank.
The height is about 65.
It's about 6.5 cm.
OK.
Then let's align this pattern.
After that, let's sew it to the edge.
It starts from the middle.
So it's like this.
Add it to the side.
OK.
It's obvious that the shape of this pattern doesn't look like what we want.
Look, the length of this line seems to be longer.
No, this is normal.
OK, let's continue.
Then this pattern needs to be adjusted to it.
Because it is a rectangle now.
But actually, according to this pattern,
it should be rounded up like this.
Rounded up.
So now I can use our extension pattern tool.
You can find the extension tool in our 2D tool bar, the third one, and then we find the extension panel line.
This tool is also updated in our new version.
When we were using this tool before, if you are a left and right symmetrical link, you need to remove the link here and then extend it.
Now we don't need it.
Now we can do this symmetrical link.
Then we just select the upper edge and the lower edge in half.
Then we enter the value we want.
Now the first line is the upper edge.
Then the second line is the lower edge.
The lower edge doesn't move.
We change the upper edge.
For the upper edge, I want to shorten it a little bit.
Change it to 280.
You can see that when the upper edge is shortened, the whole thing becomes paste, right?
This is the effect I want.
Click OK.
When it's done, we can use it.
I'll simulate it for you.
Okay, I'm done.
And then, if we have such a face, this place is definitely not a right angle.
We need to make a curve line design here.
Then we directly switch to our built-in multiline tool.
Press the Ctrl key from this point to draw our curve line.
Draw our curve line.
Then there is a curve point here.
I'll end it here.
Then select this line.
We make a cut to it.
Cut.
Then we delete the necessary pieces.
Delete.
Then this is our one.
A face-to-face version.
Of course, we need to make a curve line for this face-to-face version.
Curve line.
Let it look like it has some details and a performance of our real craftsmanship.
Then we can convert this straight line point to a free curve point.
Then we do a right-click on this line.
There is an internal curve line.
And then for the internal curve line, we input the value of this curve.
It's 11 cm.
Then we add this expansion number to it.
Then click OK.
And then after we're done, we're going to do a curve line on this version.
Curve line inside.
Put it on top.
Then simulate it.
Okay.
Now, because the example of this version is relatively large.
It's this.
Uh.
You can't get the effect.
So I'm going to make this example smaller in advance.
For example, change it to 8.
Then simulate it again.
You can see that because my example is smaller now.
See?
It feels like it's hard to stop.
It's coming out right away.
This is much better than our single-layer effect.
Okay.
Also, there's another place where we need to curve the dragon layer.
In our this one.
We just did this shou kefu.
Shou kefu also needs to curve the dragon layer.
It's okay.
Just a little bit more.
I'll give you a little.
Okay.
Good.
So after we've done our shou kefu.
And then we've done the following.
So now we're going to do this pocket.
What about the pocket?
It's a.
Uh.
It's a shape of a performance.
We can refer to a position of its original pocket.
Open this basic line display.
That original pocket.
It's in this position.
And then it's a.
Uh.
A state that we're going to put down.
Then I want to make it a slope.
Make it a slope.
Then we use the internal shape tool.
Draw a pocket first.
A rough one.
A size.
Then I'll be more casual here.
Just casually go.
Draw a pocket of a shape.
And then.
Use the adjustment panel tool to rotate it.
Rotate it.
Open the internal line display.
And then.
You put it down.
Put it in this corresponding position.
Refer to the original position.
You can put it down.
About a position is fine.
Okay.
After it's done.
We.
Right click.
On this board.
On this internal shape.
Right click.
And then.
There's a column for the board.
Board and sewing line.
You put it out.
The same.
His sewing line.
There is also.
This is also.
Previous.
One.
Previous version of the update.
And then.
We can see this sewing line.
Take this unnecessary sewing line.
Give it to delete.
And then.
Add this board.
To the outside.
And then.
You can see.
Add to the outside.
Right.
Okay.
On the other side.
We give it.
Convert it out.
Control plus D.
And then.
Also.
Add to the outside.
Okay.
I'll touch you.
Now.
Our basic line.
The display of the internal line.
Can be closed.
It's closed.
Okay.
What about our pocket?
You can.
Wait a minute.
At the end.
Remember.
We give it.
As a rendering thickness.
And then.
To the outside.
Okay.
Now.
Our whole change.
It's almost done.
Then.
We.
Next.
Is to go.
To it.
A detail of perfection.
Here.
Save it.
That first.
Is.
To apply.
Our one.
Flour.
I am.
Directly.
To apply.
Our.
The plastic window.
Provided.
This.
Flour.
File.
Among.
The thin.
This.
Flour.
Directly.
Pull it.
Our.
This.
Body window.
Good.
Then.
Our.
Loose.
Belt.
Just.
Is not.
Always.
No.
Applied.
Flour.
Remember.
To apply.
Our.
Loose.
Belt.
Flour.
In.
This.
Is.
The.
We.
I didn't.
It.
I.
Have.
The.
Left.
Right.
Sir.
With.
A.
An.
Here.
I.
It.
An.
I.
The.
This kind of sunscreen is usually thin and has a little bit of transparent effect, right?
Let's show the appearance
First, adjust the opacity of the original fabric
It is now completely opaque
We can adjust it to about 75%
Let's take a look at the effect of this transparent
We can open this high-quality filter to see
Of course, for the final transparent effect, it needs to be confirmed by blurring
Generally speaking, the transparent effect in the 3D window is more transparent
But in the real, in our blurring engine, it's not that transparent
It's usually like this
I'm going to change it to 70% now
And then we're going to do a replacement for our texture
Delete the original texture and the hair line
There's no more below
What about the original texture?
I also have a material here
And then it's one of these
A picture like this
Then we drag this picture directly to the position of our texture
The position of the texture
Then we can see that this is a picture of our texture
What about this picture?
We can create a hair line for it
In the original version
Our hair line
We just need to drag this intensity value
It can also be generated automatically
But?
If you want to find our hair line
If you want to find it, you will find that it does not exist
It doesn't exist
You can't save it as a picture
It's just a data-generated picture
But now we can
We can generate our hair line
That's our main new feature
Automatically generate our PBR sticker in 2024.1
In addition to the hair line
Gaze pattern
Surface saturation
These pictures are all ok
Let's generate one first
Let our hair line picture
You just need to click next to this auto-generate
Automatic generation
Wait a minute
Okay, it's done
After it's done
Let's take a look at this picture now
Click on it
Did you see it
We can find a picture generated by GENERATE
Right?
Well, we can also adjust it to one of its parameters
We can also adjust it to one of its parameters
For example, I want it to have a stronger sense of momentum
Then I'll pull our strength value
Right?
I'll pull it a little bit bigger
A little bit bigger
About 60 degrees
Maybe this is the effect I want
Well, this is one of our automatic generation
One of the functions of an automatic generation PBR sticker
When I make the sticker later
I will also generate a Gaze pattern automatically
There will be one over there
I'm going to make this more detailed
Okay, now, since I changed the transparency of this fabric
The whole fabric is relatively transparent
When I hide the model
Then you can see the whole costume
It lacks some real details
What does it mean
That's what we do
Some internal structures
If our fabric is transparent
It should be transparent
The layer of the bottom layer
For example, our inner
Wait a minute
And this place must be double-sided
Even if it is not special, it must be double-layered.
Wait a minute, we have to make a drawstring.
The drawstring must be double-layered.
We are going to make a drawstring pattern of the inner patch here.
As well as the position of the seam allowance.
And the position of the collar.
We all need to do a double-layer performance.
Okay, let's do it one by one.
First of all, we do the hemline.
For the hemline, we use our hook and loop tool.
Hook and loop tool.
Okay, now.
We put this.
The position of the hemline.
Let's do the hook and loop.
Hook and loop a closed pattern.
After that,
Right click, hook and loop as a panel.
Okay, put it next to us.
Okay, and then.
There is also our position.
This position.
Let's close this reference line first.
And then when you hook here, you need to pay attention.
Our middle line.
It can also be selected.
Okay.
Okay, and then.
Set the symmetry.
Let's do the hemline.
Hook and loop.
At the same time.
We remember to change the outer line of the panel.
To fold.
Click on our shortcut.
Okay.
Then here, control plus D.
Okay, so these three panels.
We'll just add it to the inside.
Okay.
I'm using the shortcut directly here.
And then we remember to sew this place too.
Okay.
And then simulate it.
And then we do it.
We'd like to make the position of the door.
We need the position also.
There needs to be a straight line like this.
We don't need it, we can delete it.
We need to measure the length of these two lines.
Give a reference value.
569.8
And then we use this is the curve tool.
Curve tool to create a curve.
Curve tool.
This should be our height value
And then our width value is 25
And then we can see that because it is finally going to the position of our hat
To do a sewing
So this shape should be a match with this side, right?
Let's see how to adjust it to match it
First of all, I will rotate this board
Let's rotate this board
Then use the user-designed axis
Then select this reference line
Then select this line and turn it over
After turning it over, we can use our edit board tool
Select these two points for a subtraction
After subtracting, we will align this point to the top
Then we use our edit circle tool
Pull this line
OK
Then change it
After changing it, we turn this board back
Or rotate
Then this time we use the first one
Reset along the line direction
After resetting, we will lay the board a little bit
Then our board is done
Then sew it
When sewing
We also use our line sewing tool directly
A pair of more sewing
Is there a length difference just now?
Let me take a look
I know
My data just now
Sorry
I am sensitive to numbers
You see 569.8
OK
Then should we put this line right?
Change the length
569.8
OK
Then this time
We should use this end
Start
Not good
This change is not good
Then we can just pull it
And then calculate this
569.8
I just said 596.8, right?
596.8
I will count it
596.8 minus 569.8
OK
Wait a minute, 696.8, 569.8, OK, this should be right.
32.1 is still missing, OK, I'll just drag it.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
In fact, it's OK to just use that number.
Well, let's choose these two overlays, and then add them to it.
I'm sorry, because I'm not very sensitive to numbers.
So just now, um,
I made you laugh.
It's okay, we can all adjust it.
Remember to fill in the seam line here.
And the bottom.
We'll just align this flat sheet.
Add it to the inside.
OK, this is our door.
And then, uh, the rest.
Oh, there's another one.
It's the back.
The back of this place.
We also need a backstitch.
If it's a backstitch, we'll just draw a flat sheet.
Draw a flat sheet.
And then?
It's also our GOLO container tool.
Why can't I reach it again?
Just draw with any ل.
Make the backless.
Right, forgot to add it.
When you hand in the form,
let your hands on your開始 kimchi.
I wanted to do it after the end of the talk,
first of all,
I noticed that you are a little worried
when talking about sewing.
But that's not the point.
We all need to have a
How to say is the detail performance of the seam
At this time, we can directly use our sticker tool to do it
It's more convenient
Then we use a 3D sticker
Then we find the position where we need to add stickers
Start from here
Then end here
Then it will ask us which side we need to add
Then you can choose which side you want
Then simulate
Then the default
Then the default position
It should be in our
Rectangle
Rectangle to make an addition
Simulate again
Add it again
If sometimes this
Sticker
It may be
If there are any other problems
Let's add it again
On this side
What's going on
Today this
Sticker tool
Then we add it to this side
I know
It may be because I have added this sticker on this side
So if he adds it here
There may be some instability
That's it
Okay, after adding it here
Let's take a look at this place
And the position of the shoulder seam
We all need to add this
A seam of the seam
Okay, and then we have this one
The bottom position is also
Then we have to start from this side
Then go back to this end point
The position of the double machine
Okay, well, we have this inner sticker
And some of this kind of sewing detail
It's done
Then in this way
We can be more realistic
To show us some of our real clothing structure and craftsmanship
And so on
Well, let's first
Well, let's take a look at our bottom
This is a position of the neckline
We're going to give him a detail of the puller
The details of the puller
We can use our editing
Editing version tool
Select our bottom
And then?
Open the puller in its property editor
Go ahead and open it
And then we're going to give him a height
The height is defaulted to a four-centimeter
You can take a look at this puller
Let's show this grid
It's actually based on the line we chose
This is the grid of our version
Then we only need to be in this loose top position
Is the loose top position two
So it's 20
Just add the puller in this position
That's okay
After adding
We're going to simulate
You can see our grid
A detail is made
Well, if we want to see this kind of puller in more detail
Then we can directly use this
A tool for sewing wrinkles
He can go
Use this kind of shape of the line
To show our wrinkles
And then you can see here
There's a effect of some wrinkles
At the same time
We can also go to him
Do a property edit
First of all, you can edit it here
His material type
Well, I have this fabric
It's a nylon fabric
Then I chose a nylon fabric
Of course, this zipper is too much
It's a translation problem
Don't care about him first
And then we're going to
You can see him
One of the effects of this nylon fabric
The effect of this nylon sewing
Will be more detailed than the default cotton
And then we can change his width
Change to a 20
You can make it wider
Because it's gradient on top
It's slowly gone
Let's change it to a 25
And then we're going to have one of his
A strength of the line drawing
Open this little triangle
Increase the strength of the line drawing
increase
And now it's very obvious
It doesn't have to be so obvious
I'm going to make it a little bit weaker
A little bit weaker
In that case
We can show this kind of delicate one
This kind of fold
Or a fold effect
At the same time
We have other of these
The seam side of the seam
We can all do it to him
Add a seam fold
We can copy one out
And then change the width to him
Change it back to a little bit smaller
And then we're going to add it to
For example, our front position
And then the neck and shoulder line
You can add them all
And then over here
You can click to add
And we're like this
This position
This is the position of the hat
Then we can add it
Well, this doesn't have to be so strong
You can make it a little bit weaker
The number is a little bit smaller
To show some of this
This kind of detail of the fold
Thank you
Including the position of our pocket
You can use the free sewing wrinkle
In the pocket of this circle
To add
What about the inner line
If you're not sure which side it is
You can open both sides
Don't open both sides
Both sides have it
That's our sewing wrinkle
What about this thing
It doesn't affect our simulation
So after you add it
You don't need to re-model our clothing
It's just an appearance
Okay, let's do it here
Let's add the wrinkle
What about the wrinkle
We add it to this position
So first we're going to do it
An addition to the inner circle of the wrinkle position
Here we add an inner circle
If it's straight, give it an eight
Then go to the right and convert it to a hole
After converting to a hole
We're going to break through the window
The material file holder
Find one of us
Pull the rope
Pull the rope and hang it
And then add this file to the work area
Let's save it first
The two parameters of the puller
is
how to understand it
The two parameters of the puller
Let's talk about it again
What about the puller
Let's take a look
Well, I just talked about the puller here
One is the interval
One is the height
What about the interval
It actually refers to our one
The size of the particle structure
It's the width of this point and this point
If it's one, it's going to be a little bit smaller
It's a millimeter
What about the height?
It's the height of the line you added to this place
OK
Let's talk about that
After we add this puller
Give it a sewing
Sewing
Just use our line sewing tool
Let's put this puller board first
Give it a little overlap
Before sewing
We need to add a position of our sewing
Add an internal multidirectional line
On the inner layer of this board
One millimeter
Then use our line sewing tool
And then before we simulate it
I'm going to take these two boards first
OK, then we're going to take these two boards first
Adjust the position in 3D
We come to a 4
Then put the positioning ball
Show it to it
Then turn it around
Move it
As much as possible
It won't be when it's simulated
It's just
It's very far away from our clothing
Then we do a little reverse selection
Then freeze our other boards
The already simulated board
Simulate
Then we'll add this puller
After adding
We can untie other boards
Add the texture of our puller board to it
In the live material
It also provides you with a texture chart
And then we'll just add it to it directly
To our
The material above
Let's add some color to it
The original text was a little bit black
And then here
Just give it directly
The strength of such a line drawing is enough
OK, so this is one of our pullers
OK, so finally
Let's add a sticker
Add a sticker
For the sticker
We'll use our
A sticker provided in our material document holder
It's one of our clothes
Graphic sticker
Drag it directly onto our clothing
Let's adjust the position
2D and 3D can be adjusted
After that
Let's focus on looking at our one sticker
So first of all
Let's talk about this simulation
The simulation just talked about
We can also go to automatically generate
Click on it
After that
We can be in this picture
On the basis of the generated
Adjust it
We're going to open it here
Open the text editor
Three points
And then we're in the text editor
We can also edit the color
And then we can adjust the effect of this picture
After we select this picture
Here are some parameters that can be edited
First of all, let's click on the color switch
Change the color
Then change the color number to 2
Identify the two colors on our picture
One is this dark gray
One is this light gray
We all know that the simulation picture
It's at the bottom
It should be black
There's no height, right?
OK, then this one above this one needs a picture
It should be white
So I turn it into this color
After the color
Then make a blur on its edge
Click on this blur
Open this radius
Open it
Then we blur this radius
It's for our calligraphy
When it's doing a height calculation
There's a transition
So our calligraphy will
Go for a blur radius treatment
If we were doing it in ps before
Isn't there a process of a high-level blur?
It's the same here
Click on an application and close it
Okay, what about this picture?
Let's save it and save it
Because I'm going to do another demonstration later
I'll press c first and copy it
And then I'm in my folder
Do a
Live material
Copy it to this side
Because I'm going to talk about another new feature later
May
Because when I was talking about that function
He
There's no background picture below
So I'll save it for now
Okay, and then we'll take a look now
And then we have another one
A very important new feature of 2024.1
It's our one
The effect of the sticker is preset
So we can see that in our
In the attribute editor of the sticker
On the top of our type
Now there's an effect preset
So we'll click on the effect preset
There are several preset effects
The first one is default
It's an effect that we directly add
The second one is our one
Let's take a look at the array effect
The effect of the array is that you can see that it's this kind of crack
And then we have this retrofine
Retrofine
And then we have this gold
Gold
On the gold side
It's default because it's gold
It must be gold
What about this color
You can adjust it
For example, if you want silver
Then you can adjust it to white or this kind of light gray
Right
You can adjust it according to your effect
I'll adjust your light gray
Okay, and then you can adjust it to this kind of light gray
And then finally it's mixed with the plant
After you choose this one
It's actually a發現 picture
There are also change-up pictures
It's a PBR sticker that uses the same PBR as the plant
Okay
So we choose this gold
It can be high
Let's just look at it now
I'm just switching it to gold now
I want it to have this kind of metal effect
And then it's this kind of silver gray metal
And then I need its height again
We just made a change-up picture
So I'm going to make the change-up picture we just made
Give it an increase
Just made this picture, right
We'll pull it to the position of the change-up picture
And then we'll change the degree of this change
Give it to a 0.5
Give it a 0.5
I said a little bigger
1, okay
Look at 1
And then?
Everyone knows that our change-up picture
It can only be seen through this rendering
Let's open our rendering
You can see our height
You can
Okay
And let's talk about it again
It's also a small point of this update
It's our change-up picture
It's now this particle diameter
It turns out that our smallest is 1, right
I can't adjust it any further
Then we are doing some very small logos
It may be that the details of 1 are not delicate enough
We hope it can be smaller
So this update is also this one
This one
The limit is canceled for it
Now the smallest can be 0.01
But 0.01, you know
It must be calculated very slowly
So we still have to reduce this value according to demand
Can give you a book
Book a 0.05
You can take a look
It will remind you that it will consume seriously
Is it going to continue?
Then you just have to look at the effect
So this place can go to the book
Now
Let me confirm it first
Let me show you
Yes, the line
See?
You can adjust it to less than 1
Less than 1
Adjust it back
And then
Render it
Now because 4
Just now, maybe this one
This is actually related to our clothing
If the clothing is now
The particle diameter has not been reduced yet
So it's not very delicate all over here
Then after the reduction
We'll go back to rendering
OK
Well, after we do this
Our overall clothing is almost complete
Then we finally remember
To change our model posture
To our stature
Female model posture
Change to a stature
Let me show you
And then we finally
To improve the quality of the clothing
OK, if there is a detail
It may have been missed just now
This is a zipper
We change it to this double zipper
Double zipper
We choose our zipper tool
The position of the zipper
This double zipper is also very simple
After choosing
Just need to be in the attribute editor
Change it to a type
Change to a double zipper
That's it
After changing this double zipper
You can see the bottom
There will also be a zipper
Then
One direction of it
There is a double back
Relative to a double head
It's from the middle
To pull
Double back
It's the upper and lower
This kind of pull
In general clothing
It's double back
Like a bag
Maybe it's two heads
Relative to each other
OK
Then we pull
It's both sides
You can pull it
Right
OK
Because my clothing quality
Has been improved
If I go to simulate
It may be a little bit slower
But you can also see
It's now
Both sides are open
Then
There is a small detail
That is
Our
This
Pull
If you say
It is now defaulted
It's up
This is not in line with
One of our gravity
So we need to
It
Adjust it
Down
Right
Adjust it down
OK
Of course
This type
What
We can all do
Self-definition
Change to a
This kind of circular effect
Pull it back here
Pull it back
OK
Then include our
This ruler
The ruler
We can also adjust
Our one
OBJ ruler
Right
it is good
OK
Then our
This one
Clothing
The whole production
It's done
Then we can save it
OK
After saving
What about me
Will directly open
I have done
A matching
One
Clothing
Let's talk about
One of our
Some of the functions
Updating
First
Let's open
Let me open
My
This
The file
Ah
OK
Then
This
Clothing
Match
With
This
Position
Ah
This
Pants
Is
Before
Our
Jeremy
That
Episode
Make
That
Ballet
Dance
Clothing
Yes
It should be this topic
Then this
It is also
On the
You can go to
Find a similar style
Just do a dress
Then this
It is also
To download
Everyone
I also share
In this material bag
You can go
One of your own
Design
Then
We can see
After we wear
After
To this
A show
First
Our
Model
First look at this model
One adjustment
My model
Is adjusted
One of his eyes
One direction
You can see
Have you used this function
We choose
Our virtual model
And then
In the attribute editor
There is a
Eyeball control
Then we can
Through this level
To adjust
This eye
Look at this
The horizontal direction
Right
Of course
You can also adjust the vertical
But what about the vertical
Just
After the adjustment
May be
Put a little
Is there
Is
Can turn a blind eye
This effect can be adjusted
Generally
This vertical
If you do not adjust
I will not adjust
Then the eyes
I want to
Look to the right
Then we adjust
Adjust a little
Right
Then
There is a small
Also this time
One update
Is our
This
Skin type
There is a button here
Called
Model configuration
Then
In this model configuration
We also have a small update
We
In addition to
Before
You can adjust
Hair
Skin
So we have
Added a color
Let's go here
To see our eyes
You select
These colors
After
See
Shall we
Our eyes
Of course
These are the default
A few recommended
More normal
Color
We
The
New model
Can be adjusted
Is
The internal
These models
Can be adjusted
Well
Like Mia
Yuna
And
Naomi
These three models are new models, right?
And then the male model should have forgotten the name
Anyway, those new ones
After you update the material store
Those models can be adjusted
Okay, then
If you have some beautiful bronze colors, right?
You can choose your own color here
You can choose any color you want
For example, I chose a kind of pink, right?
Take a look
Yeah, you can choose any color
And then there's a reset here
Reset, you can reset the original color of the eyes
Okay, I'm sure
Okay, then let's take a look at the rendering
If it's rendering
If it's rendering, let's open it first
Simultaneous rendering
Make up
We've talked about make up before
Well, the logic is
You save our model's skin for her
Or you can just use PS to open it
Just go through PS
Just do a makeup
There was a makeup talk
I remember a live broadcast before
Okay, my picture might be a little big
I'll adjust the size of this picture
Okay, and then we put this
Uh, let's talk about this lock function
Lock camera, lock camera
What about this piece?
We can see
When I click here to lock the camera
And then I'm here
If I say I changed to another position
Ah, even if I turn on this synchronization
Even if I turn on synchronization
It will still maintain
A before me
Synchronization angle
In this way, it is convenient for us
In the 3D window
To make some lighting adjustments
And does not affect me
The final synchronization of this picture is a view, right?
So this function is also mentioned by everyone before
Then we are in this time
A very useful function released in the new version
Okay, and then we're here
Let's talk about one of our HDR pictures
Uh update
Well, this update is a new function of the last version
We can also use it here
Take a look at this one of our lights
On the side of the light
We have a skylight
The environment map of the skylight
It is an hdr file
Then we are here
Open this window of this rendering
Uh, open it, open it
And then we're going to add it here
One of our self-defined lights
Ah, the self-defined light
I have pre-existed
The file of the light we predicted
For example, I open this one
This file
Okay, and then I'm going to do a synchronization of it
synchronization
I think it's because I turned on the live broadcast
So today this
The speed of the computer is a bit slow
Okay, and then
It's a little bit smaller
Take this lock
I have to take this lock off first
Okay, let's take a look
When we don't have it
When we don't make any adjustments
This hdr picture is in the background
When it's in the background
It's often this size will be lost
Right?
Then we can use this to control the size of the round top
Let's open this
Okay, after opening it
We can see that he can adjust
The radius of this round top
And then the height of the ground projection
And the ground mixing
Let's take a look
I'm going to rotate the angle of this light
Let's turn around a little bit
For example, I turn to a position like this
Okay, you can take a look
The radius of this round top is now six
If I say I shrink it
Shrink shrink shrink
See our background
See it
Does it become very small
It's a round top
It's getting very small
Okay, so if I zoom it in
So we can control the radius of this round top
This hdr environment picture
Because it's a 360 degree
One
A picture
So you can adjust its size to
More in line with your current one
One of the effects of the show
A perspective
And then the height of this ground projection
It's a adjustment of our top and bottom
I'll adjust it for you to take a look
See
The bigger my value is
Is the ground running backwards?
Right
The smaller the number
It's going down
Right
And then the ground mixing
Maybe we need to take a look at this
This this
The position of this corner
I don't know if the effect of this picture is obvious
If it's that kind of grassland picture
It might be a little bit more obvious
This picture may not be very obvious
But you know
It's us through these three values
Is able to achieve our
An effect adjustment of this environment picture
Will be much better than before
Okay, so that's all we have for this live broadcast
And then if you have any questions
You can ask in the comments
Directly take the picture as a 3D background picture
Is a different effect
Yes, the picture doesn't work
The picture, because it's not the one
360 degree one
Environment picture
Yes, it's different
This is in the light position
To add a picture
To light
Under the properties of light
The location of the environment picture of our skylight
To increase
Its format is one of our HDR
Or a format file of EXR
And then where is this format file
We can actually do it
Search HDR on the website
And then there are a lot of such free material websites
I have these lights
Also from those material websites
You can download it for free
You can also find some of your own
Find the right one
To match our clothes
Is there a system
No system
Are you talking about one of our live broadcasts?
Yes, I have shared
And then where to share
Let's talk about all our free materials
We are in the public number
Let's take a look at our public number
In our lower left corner of the public number
And then you are in the dialogue box
Just go to the free material
It will talk about all of us
Free materials shared in the past
The latest is this issue of mine
System teaching
I don't know if I understand it wrong
Misunderstanding
Teaching
It seems that there is no teaching right now
How do you think it is?
Yes, I think it is
Is there anything else?
I think it is
Yes, I think it is
I want to have a question
But I don't have one
Do you have any questions for this live broadcast?
I am just using a video
Yes, we have teachings
Oh, I was wondering if you were asking if there is a system of teaching, is it just such a video course that starts from the entrance?
In this case, we have it. It is also in our official Bilibili account.
There is a basic teaching content for you, so you can take a look after the class.
Okay, if you don't have any questions, then we will end this live broadcast.
Thank you for watching. See you next time. Bye bye.
It's time to end the broadcast.
How do you explain the angle of the curvature line?
The angle of the curvature line means that we have two points.
If the board is flat when it is curved, it is 180 degrees, right?
So the angle of the curvature line is 180 degrees.
But if you have some positions that want to make the effect of bending,
then we can change the angle of the curvature line to, for example, if it is bent, it is straight, it is 0 degrees.
It is bending inward.
It is not 0 degrees outward, but 360 degrees inward.
In fact, the angle of the curvature line is the same as the angle of the curvature line inward.
Right.
When do you want to enter the data?
The fabric generator.
Is it the fabric generator?
We have it.
We have the function of a fabric generator.
Then we are in the main menu.
Now we have adjusted our UI.
There is a fabric generator at the bottom of the tree.
Then we can use it according to the type of your fabric.
For example, my denim cloth.
And then the ingredients of our fabric.
The ingredients of your denim cloth may be cotton and dylen, right?
Or cotton and aniline.
Then you enter the corresponding value.
For example, 95% cotton and 5% aniline.
It adds up to 100%.
Then the weight.
Well.
Sticker.
OK.
We have it.
We put this preset.
Use CLO's preset text.
We all have it.
It's all there.
That is, every type of fabric will correspond to three preset text.
Folding.
We have a video of folding.
You can go directly to the episode of folding.
I won't talk about it here.
The draw parameter is the adjustment network.
Do you understand?
You can understand it this way.
The draw is actually a division of the network of the position you choose.
And then its layout is that kind of tree-shaped network.
So it can achieve a delicate simulation of the effect of this draw.
OK.
Is there any more questions?
Thank you.